Encounters are mysterious! But the world is even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والعالم تلفّه طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
There's a stinger behind the sweetness!
!هنالك لسعة وراء الحلاوة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ دماغه لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
That hurts...
...هذا مؤلم
Dad, isn't President Yamazaki the head of Yamazaki Development,
أبي، أليست الرئيسة يامازاكي هي رئيسة شركة يامازاكي للتطوير نفسها
the company you did a bodyguard job for during that blackmail case?
التي قمت بحراستها أثناء قضيّة الابتزاز السابقة؟
What were you invited to today?
لمَ قامت بدعوتك اليوم؟
She says she has a favor to ask of the nationally famous Mori Kogoro!
تقول أنّها تريد طلب معروف من المتحرّي !ذائع الصيت وطنياً، موري كوغورو
Welcome! Mori-sama, yes?
مرحباً! أنت موري-ساما، صحيح؟
Aihara Shingo (53) Caretaker
(آيهارا شينغو (53 مدبّر المنزل
The president is expecting you!
الرئيسة بانتظارك
Please come in!
تفضّلوا
Mori-sama is here.
وصل موري-ساما
Right this way!
تفضّل
Hello!
مرحباً
Welcome, Mori-san.
مرحباً يا موري-سان
Yamazaki Hiromi (50)
(يامازاكي هيرومي (50 رئيسة شركة يامازاكي للتطوير
I'm sorry to call you all the way
أعتذر على استدعائك
into the mountains like this.
لأعماق الجبال هنا
Oh, I see you're as beautiful as ever!
البتّة، لا تزالين باهرة الجمال كالمعتاد
Oh, you're a flatterer.
يا إلهي، معسول الكلام
Let me introduce you. This is the Mayor of Iwami, Hachimaki-sama.
دعني أعرّفك، هذا عمدة بلدة إيوامي، هاتشيماكي-ساما
I'm Hachimaki Hachibe.
(هاتشيماكي هاتشيبي (62 عمدة بلدة إيوامي
Hachimaki Hachibe (62) Mayor of Iwami City
أنا هاتشيماكي هاتشيبي
It's an honor to meet the distinguished Mori Kogoro-san like this!
يشرّفني لقاء المرموق موري كوغورو-سان وجهاً لوجه هكذا
It's a pleasure to meet you.
سرّني لقاؤك
Nakamura Eri (32) Pres. Yamazaki's Secretary
(ناكامورا إيري (32 سكرتيرة الرئيسة يامازاكي
I'm Nakamura, her secretary. It's nice to meet you.
أنا السكرتيرة ناكامورا، سُررت بلقائك
The pleasure's all mine.
السرور لي
I'm Aihara, the caretaker here. If you need anything, just let me know.
أنا مدبّر المنزل آيهارا، اطلبني متى احتجت شيئاً من فضلك
Nice to meet you.
سرّني لقاؤك
Now if you'll excuse me.
اعذرني الآن
What's this model of?
ما هذا النموذج؟
You know not to touch, Conan-kun!
لا تلمسه يا كونان-كن
It's all right.
لا أمانع
Mori-san, this is the Iwami Spa Resort we're planning.
موري-سان، هذا منتجع الينابيع المعدنيّة لإيوامي الذي نقوم بتخطيطه
Aside from the hot springs, it'll have a golf range, a tennis club,
بالإضافة للينابيع، سيحوي ملعب غولف ونادي كرة مضرب
an arcade, and many other facilities!
ومركز ألعاب فيديو، والعديد من المنشآت
Our city's population is dwindling, so I've teamed up with
تعداد بلدتنا السكّاني ينخفض، فتعاونت مع الرئيسة يامازاكي
President Yamazaki to build a spa resort to give it a shot in the arm!
لبناء منتجع ينابيع ساخنة لبثّ الحياة فيها
Tomorrow is the ground-breaking ceremony!
!الغد سيكون حفل الافتتاح البهيج
And we'd like you to play a part in the advertising,
نودّ منك المشاركة في الدعاية لو أمكن
by appearing in magazines and television commercials as a model.
عبر الظهور في الملصقات والدعايات التلفزيّة كعارض
Model in your commercials?!
!عـ-عارض في الدعايات التلفزيّة؟
Like this, perhaps?
هكذا ربما؟
You're getting too excited...
أنت متحمّس جدّاً
Let's set aside the business talk for now.
لننهِ كلام العمل هنا
Aihara... prepare the early celebration.
آيهارا، حضّر للاحتفال الأوليّ
Yes, I'll bring it right now!
!حاضر! سأجلبه فوراً
An afternoon with a rare feast and sake... There's nothing better!
،مأدبة نادرة في الظهيرة وساكي !لا شيء أروع من هذا
Wild boar stew and fresh Iwami vegetables!
حساء خنزير بريّ وخضروات إيوامي طازجة
They all share the simple flavors of this region!
!تحمل كلّها نكهات المنطقة
Yes, local cuisine will be one of the resort's attractions!
أجل، سيكون الطعام المحليّ أحد عوامل الجذب للمنتجع
It's coming from your upstairs office.
إنّه من مكتبك في الطابق الثاني
Pardon me a moment.
اعذروني قليلاً
Oh, yes! Mayor! Why don't you let Mori-san try the specialties?
صحيح، حضرة المعدة، لمَ لا تدع موري-سان يجرّب الشيء الخاصّ؟
Oh, that? Leave it to me!
تقصدين ذاك؟
Hey! Aihara-kun! Bring you-know-what out!
!آيهارا-كن! أحضر ذاك الشيء
What's he doing?
ما الذي يفعله؟
What are "the specialties"?
ما هو الشيء الخاصّ؟
You'll just have to wait and see!
عليك الانتظار لترى
Aihara-kun!
!آيهارا-كن
Oh, you're on the phone?
ماذا؟ أنت على الهاتف؟
Uhh, please send over one case of beer and juice!
!إذاً، أرسلوا صندوق جعّة وصندوق عصير
I'm taking you-know-what.
سآخذ ذاك الشيء
Oh, okay!
حسناً
Now these are the pride of our town!
!هذا فخر بلدتنا
W-What are they?
ما هو بالضبط؟
Newt and wasp sake! They're incredibly revitalizing!
!ساكي سمندل ودبّور، يعطيك حيويةً كبيرة
Well, drink up!
!هيّا، اشرب
I think I've had too much to drink. I need some fresh air.
يبدو أنّي شربتُ الكثير، أحتاج لتنشّق هواء طلق
Are you all right?
أأنت بخير؟
Y-Yes, I think so.
أجل، أظنّ ذلك
It was such nice weather earlier, too...
كان الطقس صحواً قبل قليل
Mountain weather does change quickly.
طقس الجبال سريع التقلّب
Like they say, a woman's heart is as fickle as autumn weather.
"تعرف القول المشهور، "قلب المرأة أشبه بسماء الخريف
Th-That was President Yamazaki!
!كـ-كانت تلك الرئيسة يامازاكي
Call the police and a doctor!
!اتّصلي بالشرطة وبطبيب
Right!
!حاضر
A balloon...
...بالون
An insecticide spray?
بخّاخ مبيد للحشرات؟
It's too late.
لا جدوى
Madam!
!رئيسة
This is horrible!
هذا فظيع
Umm, are you the famous detective, Mori Kogoro-san?
المعذرة، أنت المتحرّي الشهير موري كوغورو-سان، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
I'm Suzuki, a resident police officer.
أنا ضابط شرطة مقيم، اسمي سوزوكي
This is Dr. Sakurai, who runs a clinic in town.
وهذا الطبيب ساكوراي الذي يدير عيادةً في البلدة
Thanks for coming.
شكراً على قدومك
Well, I leave the rest to you. I'm going to have a look at her room.
سأترك الباقي لك إذاً، سأذهب لتفقّد غرفة الرئيسة
This door locks automatically, you know.
هذا الباب آليّ القفل، صحيح؟
I know that!
!أعي ذلك
Mori-san! I have a spare key!
!موري-سان! جلبتُ المفتاح البديل
It smells like insecticide!
!هذه رائحة مبيد حشرات
It appears it was locked from the inside.
يبدو أنّها كانت مقفلةً من الداخل
It appears she broke the window to get onto the veranda,
يبدو أنّ الرئيسة حطّمت النافذة وخرجت للشرفة
and then she fell over when the rail she was leaning on broke.
ثمّ سقطت عندما انهار السور الذي كانت تتكئ عليه
But why?
لكن لمَ؟
Mori-san.
موري-سان
Dr. Sakurai says she died of head injuries when she fell.
قالت طبيب ساكوراي أنّ سبب وفاتها كان إصابة رأسها عند السقوط
This office has an automatic lock,
،هذا المكتب آليّ القفل
and all upstairs windows were locked from the inside.
وكانت كلّ نوافذ الطابق العلويّ مقفلةً من الداخل
It'd be impossible to sneak past us on the first floor to go upstairs.
يستحيل أن يتسلّل أحد أمامنا في الطابق الأوّل ويصعد الأدراج
And sneaking in via the chimney would also be impossible.
والتسلّل من المدخنة غير ممكن أيضاً
So it was a completely locked room...
أي كانت الغرفة مقفلةً بالكامل
This is--!
...هذا
Say, officer! This is a bee, right?
حضرة الضابط، هذا دبّور، صحيح؟
That's a yellowjacket wasp.
إنّه دبور السترة الصفراء
Come to think of it, Dr. Sakurai did find sting marks on her head.
بالمناسبة، وجد الطبيب ساكوراي آثار لسع دبّور على رأسها
Sting marks?
آثار لسع دبّور؟
Are wasps common in this area?
هل الدبّور منتشر في هذه المنطقة؟
Yes.
أجل
Come to think of it, wasn't she afraid of wasps, Nakamura-san?
بالمناسبة، ألم تكن الرئيسة تخاف الدبّور يا ناكامورا-سان؟
Yes.
بلى
She's from here, and she'd had a traumatic childhood experience.
إنّها من أهل البلدة، وقالت أنّها مرّت بتجربة فظيعة في صغرها
Some wasps stung her in the sixth grade,
،لسعها دبّورٌ عندما كانت في الصفّ السادس
and Aihara-san saved her on the verge of death.
وأنقذها آيهارا-سان وهي على مشارف الموت
She said she hired him to take care of the mansion
تدين له بحياتها، لذا قرّرت تعيينه
because she owed him her life...
للاهتمام بالمنزل وفقما سمعت
Yes, that's right.
أجل، صحيح
I always had bug spray on hand to keep wasps from coming inside.
كنتُ أحتفظ بمبيد حشرات بالمتناول كيلا يدخل الدبّور
There've been many wasp-related incidents so far this year.
الحوادث المتعلّقة بالدبّور كثيرة هذا العام وتجاوزت الأرقام السابقة
I've figured out the killer!
عرفتُ القاتل
It was the wasps that killed her, no question about it!
!إنّه الدبّور بلا شك
Listen... President Yamazaki must've been attacked
اسمعوا، لا بدّ أنّ الرئيسة يامازاكي تعرّضت
by wasps that entered through that fireplace.
للهجوم من قِبل سرب دبّور دخل عبر المدخنة
She tried using the nearby bug spray,
،حاولت استعمال مبيد حشرات بالقرب
but in her panic, she went through the window and onto the veranda.
لكن تملّكها الهلع، وحطّمت النافذة وهربت للشرفة
Then, as luck would have it, the handrail broke and she fell over.
لكن لسوء حظّها، انكسر السور الذي اتّكأت عليه فسقطت
In other words, this was an accident.
أي أنّه كان حادثاً
But why did she escape through the window and not the door?
لكن لمَ هربت عبر النافذة وليس عبر الباب؟
When people panic, they lose the ability to make good judgments.
عندما يتملّك البشر الهلع، تضعف قدرتهم في اتّخاذ القرارات الصائبة
What's this sticky stuff?!
ما هذا الشيء الدبق؟
This is--!
...إنّه
This might not have been an accident!
!ربما لم تكن هذه حادثة
It's possible it was a murder plotted by one of these people!
من المحتمل أنّها جريمة قتل من تخطيط !أحد الأشخاص في الداخل
Protective clothing for handling wasps!
!ثياب حماية للتعامل مع الدبّور
These two bottles were used recently.
يبدو أنّ هاتين القنّينتين اُستعملتا مؤخراً
Ether and sulfuric acid?!
أثير وحمض كبريتيّ؟
Helium? Why is this here?
هيليوم؟ لمَ يوجد هنا؟
Wait a minute!
!لحظة
As I recall, it went downstream!
وفقما أذكر، فقد اتّجهت مع مجرى النهر
Fishing line and a ripped plastic bag!
خيط صيد وكيس بلاستيكيّ ممزق
And this black dirt!
وهذا الوسخ الأسود
The rain cap that should be on this chimney is gone.
غطاء المطر الذي يُفترض وجوده في العادة قد نُزع
Some of the soot inside it has been rubbed off.
توجد آثار لإزالة بعض السخام في الداخل
Scotch tape?!
شريط لاصق؟
A hole in the floor?
ثقب على الأرض؟
Ah! Now I see how the trick worked! That person is the killer!
!فهمت، عرفت الحيلة الآن !القاتل هو ذاك الشخص
Conan-kun! Where are you?
كونان-كن! أين أنت؟
Where'd that runt disappear to?!
أين ذهب ذاك الصبيّ؟
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
You always worry us when you suddenly disappear!
!تشعرنا بالقلق عندما تختفي فجأةً هكذا
Quit scampering around! Come with us!
!لا تتجوّل في المكان! اتبعنا
Hold on. Have a nap and leave the rest to me, old guy.
مهلك، لتسترح قليلاً وتترك الباقي لي يا عمّ
What the--?
ما هذا؟
Dad! What was that sound?!
أبي! ما كان ذاك الصوت؟
What was that?!
ما الأمر؟
What happened?!
ما الذي حصل؟
I've figured it out, everyone.
اكتشفتُ الأمر يا سادة
This was a murder.
كانت هذه جريمة قتل
It wasn't an accident?!
لم يكن حادثاً؟
Why do you say that now?
لمَ لم تذكر الأمر إلى الآن؟
To catch the killer off guard. I wanted time to gather proof, you see.
لجعل المجرم يهمل، فقد كنت أريد وقتاً للبحث عن دليل
The person responsible murdered President Yamazaki
قتل المجرم الرئيسة يامازاكي
and made it look like an accident.
وجعله يبدو حادثاً
What proof do you have to--?
أيّ دليلٍ لديك؟
Have a look at the inside doorknob.
انظروا لمقبض الباب، المقبض الداخليّ
What about it? Nothing seems out of the ordinary...
أهنالك خطبٌ به؟ لا نرى شيئاً عليه
Underneath the connecting part.
أسفل وصلة ربطه
This is--!
...هذا
Yes... honey.
أجل، عسل
If wasps attacked you inside, you would normally run out the door.
إذا هاجمك الدبّور في الغرفة، فستهرب عبر الباب في العادة
But there were a bunch of wasps on the honey-covered doorknob,
لكن كانت هنالك جماعة دبابير على المقبض المغمور بالعسل
so President Yamazaki ran in the opposite direction, to the window.
فهربت الرئيسة يامازاكي عبر النافذة في الجانب المقابل، في عجزها عن فتح الباب
The rail on the veranda was quite corroded.
كان سور الشرفة متآكلاً لحدٍّ كبير
It had been corroded in advance using sulfuric acid.
وتمّ إتلافه سلفاً بحمض كبريتيّ
But what about the wasps?
لكن ماذا عن الدبّور؟
Yes... the wasps were planned too.
أجل، كان الدبّور ضمن الخطّة أيضاً
Have a look at the ceiling behind you.
انظروا للسقف وراءكم
Is that the balloon that--?
...أيمكن أنّ ذاك البالون
Yes.
أجل
It's the balloon you and Conan saw on your way down to the river.
إنّه البالون الذي رأته ران وكونان في طريق نزولهما للنهر
It got stuck to a tree branch downstream.
علق بغصن شجرة في اتّجاه مجرى النهر
Ran, check the plastic bag.
ران، تفقّدي الكيس البلاستيكيّ
Okay.
حسناً
A wasp!
!دبّور
The killer put wasps into the bag attached to the balloon
،جمع المجرم دبابيراً في الكيس المربوط بالبالون
and placed it in the chimney.
ووضعه في المدخنة
They were probably gathered after spraying them with ether.
ذلك بعد تنويمها ببخّاخ الأثير غالباً
Aihara-san.
آيهارا-سان
I found a beekeeper outfit that smelled of ether in the shed.
يوجد زيّ نحّال تفوح منه رائحة الأُثير في المخزن، أليس ذلك؟
Most everyone in this area has one.
إنّه موجود في كلّ منازل هذه المنطقة
Then what are the helium tanks in the shed for?
ما الغرض من أسطوانات الهيليوم في المخزن إذاً؟
We made balloons for kids at the summer festival.
نفخنا بالونات للأطفال في المهرجان الصيفيّ
They're what's left over.
وذلك ما بقي
I wonder. There were three tanks.
أحقّاً ذلك؟ كانت هنالك ثلاث أسطوانات
Are you sure you didn't do a lot of test flights of a balloon
ألم تقم بتجارب طيران بالون متكرّرة
What's that supposed to mean? What are you trying to say?!
!ما قصدك؟ ما الذي تلمّح له؟
Only the caretaker here could have set all this up!
من كان بإمكانه ترتيب كلّ تلك الأشياء هو مدبّر المنزل الذي يعيش هنا فحسب
Yes! You're the killer, Aihara-san!
!أجل، المجرم هو أنت يا آيهارا-سان
Wh-What are you talking about?!
!ما-ما الذي تقوله؟
I was in the living room when she fell!
كنتُ في غرفة المعيشة عندما !سقطت الرئيسة يامازاكي
I was with all of you! How could I have killed her?!
!كنتُ رفقتكم! فكيف أستطيع قتلها؟
First, to temporarily keep the balloon inside the chimney,
بدايةً، لإبقاء البالون الذي وضعته داخل المدخنة هناك مؤقتاً
you tied fishing line to it, led it to the downstairs kitchen
ربطت خيط صيدٍ به، ومددته للمطبخ في الطابق السفليّ
through a small hole in the floor by the fireplace, and tied it to a nail.
عبر ثقبٍ صغير في الأرض بجوار الموقد، وربطته بمسمار
You also stuck fishing line to a piece of tape on the bag
ربطت خيط صيد بشريطٍ لاصق على البالون أيضاً
and led it to the kitchen as well.
ومددته للمطبخ كذلك
Everything was then ready to go.
هكذا اكتملت تجهيزاتك
The phone rang, and President Yamazaki went to the upstairs office.
رنّ الهاتف آنذاك، وصعدت الرئيسة يامازاكي للمكتب في الطابق العلويّ
At the same time, you were on the phone.
في الآن ذاته، كنتُ على الهاتف
Yes... you had called her upstairs office to get her into the room.
أجل، اتّصلتَ بمكتبها كي تجعلها تتوجّه له
After confirming that she had picked up the receiver,
،بعد تأكّدك من رفعها للسمّاعة
you pulled a thread leading into the kitchen.
سحبت أحد الخيطين
The tape covering a pre-made rip in the bag came off
نُزع الشريط اللاصق الذي كان يغطّي الجزء الممزّق في الكيس سلفاً
and sent the wasps flying out.
فخرجت الدبابير
The balloon blocked the chimney's top, so they flew into the room.
كان البالون يحجب الجانب العلويّ للمدخنة، فدخلت الدبابير الغرفة
The agitated wasps then attacked President Yamazaki.
وهاجمت الدبابير المستثارة الرئيسة يامازاكي
While spraying the insecticide, she headed for the door.
توجّهت للباب وهي ترشّها بمبيد الحشرات الذي كان في مكتبها
But she was unable to open it. Because it was crawling with wasps.
لكنّها لم تستطع فتحه، فقد كانت الدبابير متجمّعةً على مقبض الباب
With no other choice, she ran around the room, broke the window,
لم يكن أمامها خيار آخر، فاستدارت وحطّمت النافذة
and leapt onto the veranda.
وقفزت إلى الشرفة
She leaned against the rail and aimed the spray at the wasps,
اتكأت على السور، ووجّهت البخّاخ نحو الدبّور
but the rail broke and she fell over.
لكن انهار السور، فسقطت لحتفها
After we rushed outside, you quickly returned to the kitchen
بعدما هرعنا للخارج، رجعت للمطبخ من فورك
and undid the other thread.
وحللتَ الخيط الآخر
And so the balloon went flying out of the chimney.
وهكذا غادر البالون المدخنة
That's what Ran and Conan happened to see.
وذلك ما شهدته ران وكونان
But something didn't go as planned.
لكن وقع شيءٌ خلاف حساباتك
The balloon was supposed to fly far off into the distance,
كان يُفترض أن يرحل البالون لمكانٍ بعيد في الأفق
but the light rain and wind unfortunately got it stuck in a tree.
لكن لسوء حظّك، علق في غصن شجرة بسبب المطر الخفيف والرياح
I found the tape!
!وجدتُ الشريط اللاصق
And there is a hole in the floor!
ويوجد ثقبٌ على الأرض بالفعل
That doesn't prove anything!
!لن ينفع هذا كدليل
Aihara-san. Could you show us the towel on your hip?
آيهارا-سان، هلّا أريتنا المنشفة على خصرك؟
Towel?! Wh-What about it?!
المنشفة؟! ما-ما بالمنشفة؟
The doorknob must've been entirely covered in honey.
يُفترض أنّ مقبض الباب كان غارقاً بالعسل
Are you sure you didn't wipe it away with your towel?
ألم تمسحه بتلك المنشفة؟
There is honey on it!
!يوجد عسلٌ عليها بالفعل
And one more thing.
وشيء آخر
Please take out what's in your right pants pocket.
أخرج ما في جيب بنطالك الأيمن رجاءً
What's the matter? Show it to us.
ما الخطب؟ أرنا
That's the very same thread that undid the tape on the plastic bag.
ذاك هو الخيط الذي خلع الشريط اللاصق من على الكيس البلاستيكيّ
The mayor and Conan had barged in just then,
آنذاك، فاجأك العمدة والكونان بدخولهما
so you hastily stuffed it into your pocket.
فأقحمته في جيبك في عجلة
It appears you didn't have time to dispose of the evidence.
يبدو أنّك لم تمتلك وقتاً للتخلّص من الدليل
That, or you lowered your guard when it was deemed an accident.
أو أهملتَ عندما افترضنا أنّه حادث
Making me the caretaker because I saved her life was nice and all,
كان تعييني مدبّر المنزل لإنقاذي ،حياتها لافتةً جميلة
but I wound up like a worker bee slaving away for the queen bee.
لكنّها جعلتني أكدّ في العمل كنحلة خادمة لملكة النحل
But she said she'd make me manager of the spa resort,
قالت أنّها ستجعلني مدير منتجع الينابيع الساخنة إذا اكتمل إنشاؤه
so I tried so hard to endure it!
!فصبرت واجتهدت
But it was a lie. A big, fat lie. I couldn't stand it anymore.
.لكنّها كانت كذبة، كذبة بالكامل لم أعد أستطيع الاحتمال
I wanted to ruin tomorrow's ground-breaking ceremony.
أردتُ إفساد حفل الافتتاح بالغد
So I had to do it today.
لكن كان عليّ فعلها اليوم
Way to go, Dad! You solved the case! You're a genius, as always!
!كما يُتوقّع منك يا أبي! حُلّت القضيّة !استنتاجاتك مبهرة كالعادة
Don't be silly! That was a piece of cake!
!لم يكن ذلك شيئاً يُذكر، أشبه بوجبة خفيفة
Speaking of which, I'm hungry! Plus we didn't go to the hot springs!
بالمناسبة، أشعر بالجوع، ولم نذهب للينابيع الساخنة
Okay! Let's hit the hot springs and get manlier!
!حسناً! سأذهب للينابيع السخنة وأصقل رجولتي
Sleeping Kogoro gets to show off his mind and body!
!فرصة لكوغورو النائم ليستعرض ذكاءه وبدنه
The only thing you can show off is how to sleep...
ما يمكنك استعراضه هو النوم فقط
Whoa! What is this?!
!ما هذا؟
The room is filled with idol posters!
!الغرفة مليئة بملصقات الفنّانين
There are two of everything, even photo books and CDs!
وجد نسختان من كلّ شيء حتّى الكتب المصوّرة والأقراص المدمجة
And they have their names on them.
كما عليها اسماهما
This wasn't a suicide! It was a murder!
!لم يكن هذا انتحاراً، بل جريمة قتل
But this was a sealed room! How did the killer escape?!
لكنّها غرفة مغلقة، كيف هرب القاتل؟
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Sealed Bathroom Murder Case (Part 1)."
جريمة قتل الحمّام المغلق (الجزء الأوّل)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Adhesive tape.
شريط لاصق
Next episode takes place at the home of two beautiful sisters.
تقع أحداث الحلقة القادمة !في منزل شقيقتين جميلتين